Guide to the Auditing Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1979-1989; Accession 1991-A-067
  - Audit work papers
    - Dining Halls: Cash Sales, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Salaries and Wages, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Recording Studio, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Dishonored Checks, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Visa/Master Charge, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Miscellaneous A/R, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Salaries and Wages, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 82 - 83)
    - Salaries and Wages, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 85 - 86)
    - Bank Accounts, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Inspection, 149 York Street, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Travel Expenses, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 91 - 94)
    - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Dining Halls: Glass, Silver, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Medical School Copy Center, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - University Bank Accounts, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 99 - 100)
    - Funds Clearing, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Chemistry Stockroom, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Petty Cash Fund Counts, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - British Art Center, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 105 - 109)
    - Purchasing, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 111 - 112)
    - MIS, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Pediatrics, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - YCC Inventory, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 115 - 116)
    - TRS, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Yale University Press, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - A-110: Revision of Plans, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - A-110: Monitoring and Reporting, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Summary of Inventories, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Administrative Data Systems, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 122 - 125)
    - Physical Plant: Various, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 126 - 134)
    - Physical Plant: Various, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 135 - 137)
    - Physical Plant: Unfinished, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 138 - 142)
    - Disbursements, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 143)
    - Review of Cost Transfers, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 144)
    - Physics Overdrafts, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - Purchasing Function, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 146)
    - Athletics, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - Physical Plant: Receiving, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - Yale University Press: Financial
      - 1983 (Box 10, Folder 152 - 158)
      - 1984 (Box 10, Folder 159 - 161)
      - 1984 (Box 11, Folder 162 - 166)
      - 1985 (Box 11, Folder 167 - 170)
      - 1985 (Box 12, Folder 171 - 174)
    - YAF: Financial, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 175 - 176)
    - YAF: 1/4 Cent. Financial, 1983-1987 (Box 12, Folder 177 - 183)
    - YAF: Endowment, 1983-1987 (Box 13, Folder 184 - 189)
    - YAF: Overall, 1983-1987 (Box 14, Folder 190 - 197)
    - GPSS: Financial, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 198 - 200)
    - GPSS: Financial, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 201)
    - Art: Brissago, 1982-1985 (Box 15, Folder 202 - 206)
    - Yale Alumni Publications, 1983-1987 (Box 15, Folder 207 - 210)
    - Connecticut Academy for the Arts and Sciences, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 211 - 213)
    - Yale Child Study Center, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 214 - 216)
    - Yale Summer School of Art and Music, 1983-1987 (Box 16, Folder 217 - 230)
    - Student Loans: Permanent Files, undated (Box 17, Folder 231 - 232)
    - Financial Aid, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 233 - 244)
    - Medical and Nursing Schools Financial Aid Office, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 245 - 246)
    - Financial Aid, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 247 - 258)
    - Financial Aid, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 259 - 267)
    - Financial Aid, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 268 - 279)
    - A-110, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 280 - 297)
    - A-110, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 298 - 318)
    - HHS Proposal, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 319 - 320)
    - A-110: Attachment F, undated (Box 23, Folder 321 - 322)
    - A-110, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 323 - 334)
    - A-110, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 335 - 343)
    - A-110, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 344 - 355)
    - A-110, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 356 - 358)
- Audit records, work papers, evidence, follow up, history files and other records, 1971-1993; Accession 1994-A-131
  - Follow up Followup Audit Reports 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Audit Reports Fiscal 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Audit Reports Calendar 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Audit Reports Calendar 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Other reports Calendar 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Audit reports Calendar 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Follow up Calendar 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Audit Reports Calendar 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Audit Reports Calendar 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Audit Reports Calendar 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Audit Reports :Calendar 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Audit Reports :YSSM, 72 -185 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Audit Reports :GPSS, 176-185 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Audit Reports :Brissago, 182-'85 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Audit Reports Audit Reports :YAF, 171-86 YAF Endowment '74-186 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Audit Reports Audit Reports Audit Reports Audit Reports Audit Reports :YAF Quarter Century. '81-'86 Yale Press '72-185 Yale Alum Pubs. 78-183 CT Acad. of A&S, 173-185 SSS. 172-189 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Audit Reports :ASA, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Audit Reports :Fin.Aid. 84-85 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Audit Reports :Stud.Loans 1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Audit Reports :Calendar 1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Other Reports :and Memos, Calendar 1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Audit Reports :Calendar 1981 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Follow up :Calendar 1981 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Audit Reports :Calendar 1980 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Audit Reports :FY 1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Audit Reports :FY 1978 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Audit Reports :FY 1977 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Audit Reports :FY 1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Audit Reports :FY 1975 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Audit Reports :FY 1974 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Audit Reports :FY 1973 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Audit Reports :FY 1972 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Audit Reports :FY 1971 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - External Reports :72-73 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - C&L Report :Student loans 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Audit Reports :Investment's Office 1983 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Audit Reports :Real Estate 1983 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Audit Reports :School of Music 1982 -1983 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Audit Reports :School of Art 1983 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Audit Reports :Spanish & Portugese 1983 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Audit Reports :Communications Department 1983 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Audit Reports :Summary of dept. reviews for Fall&Spring 1983 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Audit Reports :Wire Transfers 1983 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Audit Reports :Council of Engineering 1983 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Alidit Reports :Various CMHC Documents -Aug 1989 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Audit Reports :CT financial Aid Program 1984 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Audit Reports :Physical Inspection of 451 College St 1984 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Audit Reports :Dining Hall Purchasing 1984 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Audit Reports :Construction dept. 1984 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Audit Reports :Classics Department 1984 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Audit Reports :Financial reporting 1984 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Audit Reports :TPA Books -Atticus 1984 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Audit Reports :Alumni Records 1984 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Audit Reports :General Accounting 1984 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Audit Reports :Construction Bidding Procedures 1984 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Audit Reports :Personal computers Correspondence 1984 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Audit Reports :IEC & Forestry Computer Purchases 1984 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Audit Reports:Student Records 1984 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Audit Reports:Development PC's 1984 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Audit Reports:A110 Records Retention 1984 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Audit Reports:Financial Reporting Computers 1984 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Audit Reports:Development Out Pledges 1984 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Audit Reports:German Dept 1984 (145 findings) (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Audit Reports:Ct Refining Co Complaints 1985 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Audit Reports:Construction - Cost Plus 1985 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Audit Reports:Contract Review & Bid Opening 1985 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Audit Reports:# 6 Oil deliveries 1985 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Audit Reports:Workman's Compensation 1985 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Audit Reports:Sociology Embezzlement 1985 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Audit Reports:Staff Assistant, Religious Studies 1985 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Audit Reports:Italian Deprtment 1985 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Audit Reports:Physical Inventory of Lighting Fixtures 1985 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Audit Reports:Sch. of Archicture 1985 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Audit Reports:Review of Contract & Bid Opening 1985 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Audit Reports:A-110 tests of Federal Drawdowns 1986 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Workpapers:British Art center, Cash receipts, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Workpapers:Workers Compensation, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Workpapers:Financial Operations & Planning, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Workpapers:OPS Data Center, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Workpapers, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Workpapers, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 140)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 158)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 159)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 160)
  - Workpapers, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 161)
  - History Files, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 162)
  - History Files (Box 12, Folder 163)
  - History Files (Box 12, Folder 164)
  - History Files, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 165)
  - History Files, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 166)
  - History Files, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 167)
  - History Files, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 168)
  - History Files, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 169)
  - History Files, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - History Files, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - History Files, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 172)
  - History Files, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 173)
  - History Files, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 174)
  - Workpapers, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 175)
  - History Files (Box 13, Folder 176)
  - History Files (Box 13, Folder 177)
  - History Files, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 178)
  - History Files (Box 13, Folder 179)
  - History Files (Box 13, Folder 180)
  - History Files, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 181)
  - History Files, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 182)
  - History Files, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 183)
  - History Files (Box 13, Folder 184)
  - History Files (Box 13, Folder 185)
  - History Files, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 186)
  - History Files (Box 14, Folder 187)
  - History Files, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 188)
  - History Files, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 189)
  - History Files (Box 14, Folder 190)
  - Evidence, 34001 (Box 14, Folder 191)
  - Evidence, 34001 (Box 15, Folder 192)
  - Evidence, 34001 (Box 15, Folder 193)
  - Evidence, 34001 (Box 15, Folder 194)
  - Evidence, 34001 (Box 15, Folder 195)
  - Evidence (Box 15, Folder 196)
  - Evidence (Box 15, Folder 197)
  - Evidence, 1992 December (Box 15, Folder 198)
  - Evidence (Box 15, Folder 199)